In my face, we're borrowed in Strangerware room, every whisper found a hungry crowd
Every spark became a flame They say they know what's in my heart
Like they live beneath my skin But no one sees the steepest nights
Found in random searchin' of a star
A woman slave
You've been scared enough
Cause your ex was a douche
Didn't feel your cut
That's why this
I challenge you to a douchebag
Was meant to make her claim that
Just since you were the smoothest
It works in your body
Okay, sounds good to me
Just in the weekend
I'm a faker
I've been faking this entire time
Neither one of you actually do it for me
So yeah
I'm just gonna
I'm just gonna go
what the hell neither can i you know what man i was just jealous of you i actually do like your
music i like your music too really yeah thanks for watching my feel it coming parody if you want
to check out the rest it was funny like i was funny barbeque it was funny until he like sold his
ass to china oh how are we doing i don't know maybe i'm gonna sleep soon i don't have a couple
Really good pineapple drink, whatever.
I don't know, anyone want to come up?
Gotti, you're not a very helpful person, Gotti.
You know, Gotti?
Oh, you're just gonna go blend in with it.
You know what I mean?
Have my back?
What kind of?
I made him the troll king.
He's been trolled a bit.
He just goes to sit there and like promotes his book.
And it's polite.
He still trolls me.
What, Rudy?
Come on.
Hi.
You're Rudy Meow back.
Come here.
Come on.
You're Rudy Meow.
He got his meow back.
Rudy got his meow back.
Hi.
If you remember when I got Rudy,
he was like just, I mean, he was just hiding under the bed for like a month.
But now, oh, you have some rice?
Okay, I got some rice. He's gonna eat some rice.
Um, but he's a cute cat,
and he's like really acclimated well,
and he loves me or don't you?
He's even outside. Is that good?
He's open somewhere. He's open somewhere.
This is Kinwa. Do you need Kinwa?
Oh, Rudy.
Well come up. I don't know. We can talk about anything you want. I don't I don't I mean it's like wow
I mean it's like so funny. She's like oh my gosh
I mean he brings up past and Christine's like oh isn't that true isn't that true
He raised up the past and then thing that is like what like technically one second ago is the path like anything that ever happened
Is in the past anything oh?
Yeah, that's correct. That is that's correct. I mean Christine if there's anybody there's any woman that sounded like a trunker
It's her. I mean, it's like it's crazy
But again
You know, I need a little bit more like audience participation than just like, you know people sitting here. Oh, there we go. Hi Nancy. Thank you
Well, there you go now. I'll continue streaming, but it was like I was about to stop because it's really like difficult
Just streaming without
Some kind of interaction. I don't know
Everyone's afraid or guys you don't need to be afraid like listen listen listen
I'll I'll take I'll take the I'm gonna be taking the hit no matter no matter I'll take the hit
I'm already taking it. You know, don't worry about yourselves. I mean
Seriously, it's like I'm the I'm the big fish, you know, it's like a
There's no reason to go after anybody else. No, but it's just it's just me
I'm the one easy to blame. I'm the one that can hate Bond over. Oh, I'm the biggest hate bonding mechanism of like the fucking year
What is it and then who's talking about oh?
He begging for fish tacos. How long has that been a meme begging for fish tacos if you actually go to that episode?
She she she plugs that episode you can see
It was $10 for data because I already had received the fish taco donation, which I didn't even ask for and so I mean it's like
I don't know it's like and then talk about the past. I was a year and two months ago, but it's okay
It's okay. I mean, it's like but yeah, you can see it
Yeah, it always turns back on me always. It's like it's okay. I'm just eat. I'm just an easy target. I guess I don't understand why but uh
You know for somebody that came in
Being nice and I was nice. I mean everyone everyone was an asshole when I got here. Everyone's still an asshole even worse
They're like, I mean not everybody and of course not you guys in the chat talking about other people that are you know
The biggest big mouth, but I do have their wedding picture
I know because this is it. She's like, oh my god, and they're even mad
I made like a nice picture of them like a night. It's like it wasn't even I yeah
I used their horrible pictures as the as the model for but I made them good-looking
I made them look they look like a fucking Disney movie
And even that is like, oh my God, I'm just so obsessed
or something like that.
I didn't take very long to make, but I mean, it's like here.
You can see what they look like in their wedding picture.
You know, like that.
Oh, I can't show it.
There's an issue with that triangle in a little while.
Well, I'll show you the original photos though.
I got those too.
Here's one, okay.
And here's another one.
These are your couple of the year guys.
Here you go.
Yeah, Rudy's right here. Oh, yeah
But remember where Rudy was under the bed and it's like apparently I leave my cats in the dungeon
They're just like they're so used to not taking care of and it's like, you know, everything is perfect with everybody else
You know, I've had a lot of cats since I came here, you know, some of them get it
Some of them acclimated into the neighborhood. Yeah, what the hell is that that same man? You can see your nursing Samans real picture
Let's get to that. Let's get to that. I'm us and this one's beat is real picture
Well, you didn't look different than that. No, that's what they look like. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, exactly. Oh
My gosh
I'm so yeah, I'm the prize. Yeah, that's I mean, it's like, you know, they act me they really act like monsters
I really do. I mean, it's like and even like, you know
Yeah, exactly. That's what I just said and I made them look so cute
I mean it's like look you can see like I did on my community wall as opposed to this did where I took the
I took that picture and I made them into I wanted to show I can make even monsters look like, you know
Nice people even NorCal got a lap out of it
NorCal's really not a bad dude, you know, he's a good dude actually, but I'll show you here. We go
This is what they really looked like. I did a couple pictures of that. Oh, that's not what they were looking
This is with my imagination
and talent, this is what I turned them into,
but you know, you saw the real photos, right?
Okay, here, check this out, da da da da da, here we go.
So here's one, there we go, there's one, see?
Look how nice I made it,
they look like fucking nice little,
they're mad at this, she's mad at that now,
and then there's a wedding photo.
This one's a little bit more realistic,
that's got all Vitas chins in there, yeah,
but I based it on those pictures,
but see how talented I am that I can create this, yeah.
There's there's there's so perfect though. I just want to make them so perfect like they really are and then you know
I'm a monster, but they're just perfect people, right?
Yeah
Anyway
And what's the RG RG is RG, you know, I'm trying to talk on her show and explain something but can I talk no?
All I can do is put a high-pitched voice,
imagine the most high-pitched voice like in your ear,
like, oh, and it's like, and then trying to talk,
and then it's like, they're not even letting me talk.
I let her say all the things she wanted to say
on my show today, I put myself on mute.
Hi, how are you, Noel, how are you?
Noel, Noel, I think, you know,
INX has been looking for you,
she wants more information about you and Brandon,
so if you have a second,
try to get in contact with her and drop your channel too.
Yeah, so there's Noel.
Um, hi babe. Oh, this is my baby right here. Hi Rude. Hi. Rude is probably 18 years old.
There we go. Let's see. This is how I pet my cat. See, I just go like that, but it's
like real comfortable. Oh, you want the link? Okay. Okay. The link is actually to scroll
up a little bit. You'll see it, but I'll post it again.
Yeah, this is mr. This is mr. Rudy Rudy is probably 17 18 years. Okay. Here's here's that Noel
Hi psyche. Hi, what's going on tonight?
How are how how is your day? I love your cat. You love Rudy. Yeah, that's mr. Rudy
Who wants some more information about me remember remember you're talking to this a lady Karen the other day I and X
Yeah, you mentioned Brandon Q. I think you said you've been on a date with him. Oh, yes. Yes. Yes. Yes
Yeah, she wants to talk to you, but yeah, how are you doing?
Good, I'm doing good and how we're and how is your how is your how is your day? Oh, it's pretty good pretty good
That's Rudy. You might say hi to me
What kind of the cat is that I call I just say ginger cat. He's a good ginger cat
And uh, and he's a sweetheart. He's like a little bit. He's like an old, we call him old man, but you know
Someone said oh don't call him old man because you know, he's young and hard aren't you and he's a sweet kid
But you know, he got his meow back because he used to not have a meow and now he can meow again
We're sure under under ones. You're under
Or you know, it's really hot today. It's like a hot day today. And so I think Laura and Lola are like outside
in the in the air and stuff because you know, it's really hot inside here and it's like, you know
I'm really happy that people that there's people that have indoor cats and you know
And the cats are used to that and stuff like that but my cats
They are you know, the rescues they've been used to being outside too most of the time and so and you know
Rudy was an outdoor cat. He hardly goes outside. Yeah
But you know, I do take care of my cat. I don't like the the I guess it's like a a meme or it's like a
Just something they keep repeating until everyone believes it but like that I'm abusive to animals and stuff like that
It's like so
Is the boy
Yeah, how are you, babe?
But, and he likes to go into covers.
Hey, Dougie Doug.
How are you?
I'm on you, Dougie Doug.
Hi, Dougie Doug.
Hi, Doug.
How was your day, Doug?
Yeah.
If you want to come up, Doug, and say hi.
I haven't talked to you for a while.
It'd be great to talk to you because a lot of stuff's been going on.
So, thank you.
Do you do those Nancy?
Who's Nancy?
Do I know her?
Nancy, reality Nancy.
Do you know her?
Yes, I do.
Yeah.
There she is.
That's her.
That's Nancy in the chat.
Nancy, do you want to join?
I don't think she I think she doesn't really join very much, but yeah, that'd be awesome. She would something
No, no me join. Yes, and you're subscribed to mine
YouTube. Yeah, so it's stinky. What's the numbers with it and fine nine three six?
Stinky and five nine three six. That's no well. What do you do on your channel? No, well, I do some lying
I do and I do a fun channel. I do
usual basketball games you show you show like the the handicap basketball or what's it called?
The
special Olympics special Olympics
And have you, are you an Olympic champion?
Yes, I am sort of, yeah.
And so, Nancy is in your chat sometimes, she says.
She watches and you're sometimes, she was with your dad.
Yeah, she says, I watch Noelle's live sometimes
with her dad.
You haven't, the type in there, I didn't know that was you.
Well, she says she she says you have the sweetest dad your dad's a sweet man. Yes
Yes, Ian
Okay, yes, I do the car
carry
Yo-yo
Very old him. Okay. Yeah. Yes the car carry off the yeah
Mom and my I see our dad
Yes, yeah
And they're nice people
Everyone's dad of that a mom or nice, you know, but you know, why is that? I don't know
Sometimes they don't get along with each other or sometimes they they're just like, you know, not very others your dad in the room
Hi dad. No, that's not my dad. I just
No, that's not my dad. I
You're imagining
You know somebody
Have you ever been drop dead Fred? Oh
Have you heard of that key person? He's an imaginary person, but he details ever seen drop dead Fred
Can you stop please?
Who me? I don't want to discuss that. Oh
Oh, I'm so sorry. Oh, I okay
Well, it was just a movie who was in the movie you remember that who's the movie with them that was you in the movie
we
Nancy do you have a?
Discord
Well, I don't know she has you have a discord. Oh, you know Nancy's in my in my discord
Can Nancy join mine my discord dance
That you're gonna have to remember she's in mine, so you're not to go in there and say Nancy
Here's my discord here to post your link in mine, okay?
Yeah, she said no sweetie. She doesn't have one, but she but no
She is okay, no no well
When you use that straw does all the liquid come out of the straw before it gets your mouth because there must be holes in that
Straw by now, right? No, it's not
Like opening straw
I guess your coping is right. Have you ever thought of using one of those metal straws?
You can actually bend it. No, of course not. No. No. Okay, that doesn't work.
These straws are really good for me. Yeah, those are other good for you. Okay,
well good. I'm not knocking. I'm just saying. If it was metal, you could bend it. You could
never see those people bend them. Bend them. No, I have. No, I have not. Okay. I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry. That's okay. It's okay.
Do you like Michael Jackson? Do you see Michael Jackson eating popcorn? Yeah, you saw my thumbnail. He's eating popcorn
Michael Jackson is I
like his
Songs I do is Michael Jackson is still alive
He's dead. Oh, he died. Have you you know in them? I saw a music video. It was called Thriller and he's a zombie
Yeah, he was it has all me Michael Jackson ever visited you and had dinner with your family
What oh my gosh
What are you doing to me? No, he's not that's what the fuck you're talking about
I'm so sorry. I thought he did cuz I thought he said
I'm going to know wells for dinner. Oh
What the fuck
Oh my god
Oh my gosh
gosh what the fuck my brain is stunned oh my god oh my god wow oh my god psyche are you trolling
me or something what the fuck troll i never heard of that troll he says just leave me alone
you heard that song leave me alone have you heard this one it don't matter if no wells black or
What the fuck?
She's bad
I should know it. I'm bad. I'm bad. I'm bad. You know it
Hey, noelle
What the fuck I see the Michael Jackson dance you just almost show me your dick
Oh my I did not I'm wearing a speedo and you can't see me. Are you serious? Yeah
You almost show me your dick. Oh my god. I
almost did
I didn't I did not it wasn't even almost first of all I would excuse me guys
He almost show me his bit guys
Well, I'm gonna be arrested if you keep saying stop it. Why would she be arrested? I am 26
I know, but, you know, every year, 26 is the new 16 years old.
No, it's not.
Okay, well, I don't know.
Some people seem to think that I'm being called.
Psyche.
Psyche, why are you doing this to me?
Are you just trying to fool me around, it's my brain.
No, I was wondering if you met Michael Jackson.
Oh my God, what the fuck, he's still alive.
Michael Jackson showed up here, adorable.
He's dead.
Shut the fuck up, Psyche.
Excuse me. Wow. Okay guys, can you write that to me write that down?
You want no, well to leave ask if she's had Michael Jackson for dinner
I'm just here for the turkey and stuff and Noel
Noel don't be afraid. It's just me Michael Jackson. I'm a zombie
Oopies oopy. Oh my gosh. Well, you know what it's better than
Better than you flashed better than getting flashed, right?
No, I was playing some funny stuff earlier.
I was thinking, you know, I love this guy, Bart Baker.
So funny.
I know some people were like,
why are you playing these, you know, song parodies?
You're so, hey, hey, I'm a little bit low on content right now.
Oh, excuse me.
I need, so let me see.
You want to see?
I see it.
Let me see if I find a song that we like.
Oh, this one's good.
You guys know Zane?
You heard of Zayn? This one's called I want to live forever not fame but Zayn. Okay here watch this one
We're gonna love it. I promise you. Oh my god. At least they're on their way. I think Bita called the cops
Thanks to tell us we've got to come up against it's below dark
I'm about to sing false and I'll turn to sound like I don't have balls
Hey, there's a...
You're crazy
Shut up
I say we can
And we'll die if they know
Except
We'll tell them
I'll come
To this game, you know
The thing that I have decided
If you don't come back
We'll kill ourselves
And we'll need that R
Good luck shaking that one off your winch, hey this doesn't mean we're having another three way area that was weird
Is it from a movie? Uh, no, that's like, it's like Zayn and uh, that's Zayn and uh, yeah, this is from the 9th of the Living Dead
Oh, okay. No, I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm sure that I'm sure there was a dog or type of a
I can't be a real person
Anyway, I don't mind be so mean. I know but I don't know apparently I steal I all I do is like, you know
She makes content. I just steal content
I mean, I'm only done
How many thousand thousand thousand hours without a mention of her? I don't know. It apparently I'm a
I don't know. I just I must be like the most evil person in the world, you know guys aren't I evil?
I don't know
So, oh gosh, um here you can see my alien
I'm spunky. He's holding a cat. There's my screen. You can see where I am. Hi guys
You see me? Okay
I know this alien looks like a praying mantis and so we were watching some fun stuff the other day
I thought I thought we could watch some more you guys like seeing
Crazy animals. I'm gonna do the C pig again
The C pig is like my new favorite animal. Have you guys ever heard of the C pig? Okay?
I'll show you if you haven't seen it
So this is quite some kind of name see Frank
You're gonna be impressed I think
So this is true facts about the C pig, okay, and I want you to enjoy here
This is True Facts about the C-pig.
There we go, got it, got it, got it, okay, there we go.
And there we go, there's a C-pig.
Here we will explore True Facts about the C-pig.
Here is a picture of a lamb pig.
As you can see, they are virtually indistinguishable
from the C-pig.
One way to tell the difference is that bacon from a land pig tastes delicious,
while bacon from a sea pig tastes like a fish farted on a dirty beach cracker.
Another way is to simply ask it whether it's a sea pig.
If when you ask your mouth fills up with seawater, then you're probably an idiot,
because the sea pig lives deep in the abyss of the ocean.
The sea pig is a type of sea cucumber.
This is stock video of a sea cucumber.
which has been downloaded one time. By me. This is a picture of a land cucumber,
as you can see they're virtually identical. If you get confused, check to see if your
cucumber is breathing through its anus. Because unlike land cucumbers, sea cucumbers breathe
through their anuses. As you might have guessed, this is no ordinary run-of-the-middle common
Think of it as a multi-purpose orifice, for breathing, pooping, baiting, and any other orifice-related needs you might have.
Convenient. Not what I would have chosen personally.
I'm quite happy with my arrangement. I'm a man who likes a bit of distance between the breathing and the pooping, but no judgments.
As my mother used to say, a hole is a hole.
Wow, in this context that really sounds pretty bad.
In any case, the many uses of the cloaca did not escape the pearlfish, which has formed
a symbiotic relationship with the sea cucumber.
It hides inside the sea cucumber's butt, where it feeds and gains protection.
The sea cucumber, meanwhile, has a fish in its butt.
Win-win!
The sea cucumber has a remarkable defensive adaptation.
When attacked, it violently contracts its muscles and jettisons its internal respiratory organs out
of its anus in a process known as evisceration. Needless to say, the predator becomes confused.
To understand this, imagine that you are getting mugged, and in response, you pull your pants
Further down in the depths, the little understood sea pig uses hydraulic pumps that inflate
its legs full of water as it marches on the ocean floor in search of detritus and whale
carcasses to eat. Because it is so mushy mushy, the sea pig is a host of parasites like small
snails and crustaceans which burrow into it and feed on its insides. Bummer. Fortunately,
Remember if someone scares you just bend over and fart your lungs all over that bastard
Who knows it might just work
This is Susie. Susie is in the class gastropoda, which encompasses snails and slugs.
Specifically, and by specifically, I mean specifically, and by and by I mean and by, Susie is a type of sea slug called a nudibranc.
There are around
3,000 freaky species of nudibrancs, but they come in two basic body plans.
One body plan can be seen in the ear-lit nudibrancs. They can look a bit like
claymation pubic hair.
or like a porcupine rolled around in candy corn.
Their backs are covered with floppy floppy spiky things called serata.
These serata are extensions of their digestive system.
Because why not?
But they also assist in breathing.
The other body plan belongs to the dorid nudibranch.
It is the more sluggy of the two.
Dorid nudibranchs have a sturdy, fleshy fleshy covering called a mantle.
The mantle can sometimes look like a frilly skirt, or perhaps a fashionable poncho.
Some species, like the Spanish dancer, Nudibranque, can use this skirt to swim.
Sort of. Some other Nudibranques also try the Swimmy Swimmy. But in most cases,
it looks a bit like a Muppet simultaneously auditioning for the part of the F, U, and N
in a Sesame Street production brought to you by the word fun.
It does actually look fun to swim like that, like sneezing in outer space. Up front, nudibranchs have
two rhinophores, which are kind of like nostrils that have been turned inside out.
Much like our noses can pick up the chemical signals of a fart wafting in the air, these
rhinophores can pick up chemical signals in the water. This is important because their eyes
totally suck. They are very tiny and can only sense dark and light.
Like a colorblind machinist in a Skittles factory, the nudibranch is unable to appreciate the beauty of its own decoration.
This one looks a bit like a landspeeder.
Whoa!
Except near the back where you would expect the peoples to sit.
There is a plume of gills that encircle their anus.
These gills are beautifully folded structures that maximize surface area to extract oxygen from the surrounding water.
These allow the dored nudibranch to breathe.
right next to its anus.
Before you judge, however,
to the nudibranch, this body plan might feel like an upgrade.
To understand this, let's look at some nudibranchs when they are babies.
Little baby nudibranchs look a lot like snails.
They have a shell and some even form an operculum,
a little trap door for their hidey hole.
A long time ago, the shelled ancestor of snails and slugs
got into some freaky sh** called torsion.
Torsion is a twisted change in body plan.
To understand this, imagine if you laid down on your stomach and arched your back.
Then you grabbed your left foot with your right hand and your right foot with your left
hand.
Now imagine twisting really hard so that your butt faces upwards and is right over your
face.
This is the first yoga pose they teach you when you arrive in hell.
Snails live out their lives cheerfully with this arrangement.
Every time you ask why evolution adds or removes a nipple from a cat, look it up.
However, millions of years ago, after a night of eating jalapeno chili con carne,
the ancestor of the nudibranque had enough of this head up your butt.
As it transitions to its juvenile state, the baby nudibranque loses its shell, untwists
and does its best to put all of its organs back in some semblance of order.
That is to say that the nudibranque is a bit of an unsnailed snail.
and at least its mouth and nose have a bit of distance from its gill-ringed anus.
And yes, that one does look like a Pikachu that got busy with a Swiffer.
The notobranx mouth parts are under its front parts, right between a befingered
moustachio of two feeding tentacles that can help it feel around for food.
They eat a variety of animals, many of which, like colonial tunicates,
Because the ocean is weird.
They are among the cutest carnivorous predators, and we'll even eat other slugs and nudibranchs.
This one's eating a slug called a sea hare.
Because apparently it looks like a rabbit, a rabbit who's squirt farting purple ink because
he's seriously f***ed.
If we speed it up, it looks like he's slurping a noodle.
Oh!
He'll eat with a beak and a rangula, which is basically a tongue with teeth on it, which
is crazy.
Don't French kiss a nudibranque, you'll die.
Here we see an anemone being hunted by a rainbow nudibranque, which does not look like a rainbow
at all.
More like a curtain that a cat got to, but it strikes with the vigor of a proctologist
That's like trying to tongue sponge the crumbs out of the bottom of a can of Pringles.
One group of neuter pranks in the genus Melabi has evolved a different feeding strategy.
It has traded in its tooth-tongue radula for a head in the shape of a Venus flytrap.
It uses its head like a sea floor pooper scooper, like if you used your hoodie to eat a shrimp taco.
A skeleton shrimp. Blacking a shell sea slugs including nudibranchs and this spotted sea
hare which does not look like a rabbit must get creative when it comes to defense from predation.
Some have evolved to be very good at camouflage. You see these cows? I tricked you. They're not
This one is perfectly camouflaged as an old man with his hands behind his back inspecting his garden
That's a plug reading my azaleas. That's irony. You better stop or I will assault you
That's a dad joke
What's up
Yeah, what's going on what's up with you are you are you in your car?
You're not where are you in your bedroom? You have a you have a wheel like that in your bedroom. Yeah, I do
Amazing. Okay, um, so what are you eating? I'm eating ass. Oh my god, who's
mine
Eating some ass right now. Well, so what's going on? We're working all day. No, I don't work
Don't work to just drive around in your car. No bother people pay for my living expenses
You are you coming over to my house tonight? I have psyche pay for my living expenses
You do? Yeah, I pay I pay for you to be homeless. I
Pay me somebody else $10 a month not to rent to you
Hello bang bang bang bang. Hey. Oh
What's that kill bill song bang bang or that song bang bang? I'm gonna put it in your ass
But no, thank you. I already ate. I'm like one of those those sea creatures. I used my butt your door dashing
You grew up hubbing
Yeah, you do well
Why is there a big takeout bag of food with somebody else's name on it in your driver seat or passenger seat, but
I see, I see it. I can see it reflected in your glasses, you bitch.
Why is there a black guy here?
Because you're here. I can't help it.
Thank you.
You look like an old lady driving kinda. You remember like an old lady with those glasses?
I'm not driving right now.
Oh yeah, you're in your bedroom.
I don't drive. I don't know how to drive, but I don't have a license.
I'm gonna call the cops on you then.
Oh, there's a little cat here. Oh.
Pick it up.
Oh, so cats like lost get it go pick it up and save it. Oh
You don't have to cross the street. I ran across the street. Okay. Well, it's gone forever. Well
I think I have one of your boyfriends here today. His name was um squid Squidward. You're dating this guy named Squidward. Oh, yeah
You are that's cool
Retracted to men
Yeah
Totally, that's awesome. Yeah, it's been a glow in yourself. I mean it was a little there was a little black cat. Oh
The door it did. Oh, are you sure within your just your
Do your pants back?
Bang, okay. Well anything else to add or you're just gonna make on sequiturs and
He's sick okay come back another time. We're trying to be educated on like you know, it's like different animals right now
I don't have time to listen to you say bang bang for the next, you know, 25 minutes, but
How about a mudskipper? Have you ever seen you ever seen Gilligan's Island? There's a skipper on Gilligan's Island
But this is a mudskipper right here. You want to see a mudskipper?
See I'll let you back up to watch it with me if you want, but hold on a second. I'm gonna let the mudskipper first here
Okay, oh shit
You're back with me? Okay. We're gonna watch about the mudscape, okay? You'll learn something.
I want to watch the part with the old lady there's a you, it's a you!
and by that I mean dead, but Leonard isn't dead because Leonard can breathe air.
He can do this through his specialized skin and by gulping air into his mouth parts,
which are used with blood vessels very close to the surface.
Getting around isn't easy. If your basic body plan is designed to do floaty floaty in the water,
gravity can be a bit of a bitch.
Our fish ancestors had bony muscular fins.
Fins that could evolve into strong limbs and elbows to help push against gravity as they crawled onto shore.
Jerry, what is this footage?
I'm talking about an ancient fish crawling out of the...
Well, this isn't better.
Yes, I can see she's crawling, Jerry, but she's a person.
All right, well, that's a dead fish.
But months keepers come from a different evolutionary line of fish.
Fish with floppier webbed fins.
Excellent demonstrating, Leonard.
the same line that led to the goldfish and i'm not judging the goldfish
i knew it's hard with the ping pong balls to stay fair in the toilet flushing
but you wouldn't really ask a goldfish to help you move apartments
but mudskipper don't give a crap what line he's from
mudskipper will use the parts he was given with a few little modifications
its pelvic fins on the bottom are fused to form a sort of suction cup
Imagine what you could climb if you had sticky nipples.
For a casual stroll, the mudskipper employs a movement called crutching,
which looks a little like trying to get to the remote after squat stay at the gym.
It props itself up with its pelvic fins and then pulls itself forward with its pectoral fins,
dragging its motionless tail behind.
But if the going gets rough, or it needs a bit of extra speed, the tail springs into action.
It curls and digs in and helps propel the body forward.
Whoa there, Tiger! Sorry, I have to show you the leaping blenny.
It's a different fish that uses a similar movement, but sometimes the twist gets a little out of
Having speed and good ups helps if you're a carnivore, which many mudskippers are.
It's like you're smoking a little cigar.
Yeah, see?
But eating on land brings another challenge for the fish.
Here, try this.
Lie down on your stomach in front of a chicken nugget.
Now try and swallow that nugget without using your tongue.
I can see you're not doing it.
Well then don't start thinking about your tongue.
Don't concentrate on the big, fleshy, slug-like thing filling up your mouth.
In any case, the mudskipper doesn't have a tongue.
So to swallow on land, the mudskipper seems to use water that it stores in its mouth parts as a kind of hydro-tongue.
It pushes water out of its mouth as it grabs its food, and then it kind of sucks it all back in.
And the water helps transport the food back towards the tummy parts.
Now, to prove that it was the water, they did it again.
But this time they put the food on, I quote,
the center of always ultra normal plus sanitary pads.
With the water absorbed, the food could not make its way back to the tum tum.
And the Mudskipper has an interesting story to tell his friends.
Science, the Mudskipper needs water.
It is a fish after all, and it likes to be moist.
Like that trip of sweat rolling down the small of your back into your butt crack
because you decided to wear jeans on that hike sort of moist.
moist like testicles in a freezing pool its eyeballs can retract into dermal cups that
pertain water to keep them more protection and mating the mudskipper digs burrows with its mouth
one of the bummers of not being able to use a shuttle they are very territorial animals
sometimes a simple dorsal fin displays enough to ward off a trespasser but other times
Oh, when it's time to lay eggs, the male and female retreat into the burrow.
The eggs are placed in an air-filled chamber because the surrounding water lacks oxygen.
When it's hatching time, the male gulps the air out of the chamber.
Submerged in water, the Mutskipper babies can hatch and swim up and out of their hidey
holes to the surface.
Just because you don't have the big bony muscley fins
doesn't mean that you can't do incredible things with what you are given.
That is how the Mutskipper do.
Amazing.
Do-doink-doink.
Just had first date with Karen.
She's very assertive.
Love it.
She got us free dessert because her-
True fact is not appropriate for children or adults who don't act like children
Here in the coral reef among these beautiful ocean plants there hides a seaworm. Wait, what the brightly colored things are the worms?
Okay, still beautiful, but now I feel like
Kind of like love imagine if one lived in your nostril
You'd be the fanciest lad at the party. These creatures are in the class polychaeta
They are referred to as Christmas tree worms or spiral brancous giganteous given the fact that they are on average one
Guys, we're gonna see if she wants us wants me over there or someone that person's fooling me
Costco glizzy that that that hold on is that a cue or is he say tizzy? Okay. Let's go to onyx blue onyx blue
We'll see she really wants me over there, but if not, I'll be back over here. Well, I'll go over there for a little bit
Come check it out